vend-o.com 2019-04-07

# Vendo

English   Français   Deutsch   Español

At  we are committed to honoring the privacy of our users and suppliers. This privacy policy covers the processing of personally identifiable information shared through ´s services in accordance with the EU Personal Data Protection Regulation 2016/679.

GmbH, with registered offices at Dorfstrasse 50, CH-6390, Engelberg, Switzerland, is designated data controller of your personal data.

Technology SL is our designated representative in the European Union with office in, Carrer Roselló 224, Atico, 08008 Barcelona, Spain. All communications under this Privacy Policy may be addressed to this representative by email at: [support@vendoservices.com](mailto:support@vendoservices.com) with the email subject: **GDPR**

La Agencia Española de Protección de Datos with registered offices in, Calle Jorge Juan, 6, 28001 Madrid, Spain, is designated the supervisory authority for your personal data. 

###  1\. **     What Personal Data does  process?**

We collect personal data from visitors and/or users as you navigate through and/or purchase a Product from the websites  provides payment processing Services to. 

When you use the services provided by , we ask that you give us: 

  * Your first and last name
  * Address (Country - State if applicable), 
  * Phone number, 
  * Email address 
  * Login and account details such as username, password, user ID
  * IP address,
  * Financial information such as your bank account number and /or credit card number, whichever is selected by you as the preferred payment method, 
  * Aggregated trend analytics based on users behaviour,

This information facilitates us to deliver our service to grant you your access rights to our Partner’s products and services. In order to fulfill our role as a payment provider solution,  furthermore receives from Websites with whom you placed an order, information about the online URL you will access.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. You are responsible for the accuracy of the information you provide to us and you are expected to update any information you provide us.

The legal basis for processing this data is both that it is necessary for us to be able to provide our services and, for those additional services and marketing/communications services, your informed consent set out in this notice.

###  2\. How  uses your Personal Data? 

uses your personally identifiable information solely for the purpose of providing the  services which are more particularly described herein:

  * To charge your personal bank account, credit card or preferred payment method selected by you with the amount you have consent for the service or product you have purchased,
  * To send you emails, text messages (sms), voice messages notifications about the product or service you have purchased,
  * To provide you with customer support services responding to support tickets, and helping facilitate the resolution of any disputes regarding your payment,
  * Carrying our technical analysis to improve our payment platform,
  * Carrying our internal analytical program to improve your payment experience,

**Disclosures:** To provide the services,  has to share the information provided by you with: 

Third parties entities as Data Controllers ( their processing is carried out under their Privacy Terms which you will have been provided).

  * Your bank and/or credit card company, 
  * Partner sites from where you have purchased the product or service,

We also provide your Data to our service providers for the performance of their services to us:

  * Fraud prevention and Risk management
  * Web hosting server
  * Customer service support

**Retention period:** shall not process these data any further and/or keep this data in any database longer than strictly necessary for these purposes, or due to a legal obligation. We may retain personal data beyond the aforementioned periods for legal or administrative reasons, such as defending our responsibility and complying with mandatory legal obligations, subject to applicable law.

Note that we retain the data collected from you in an anonymised and aggregated format.

###  3\. How does  market you directly about Partner’s Products and Services? 

  * **On-site marketing and communications**

We may send you an email to complete your purchase in case you have started the sign up process but never put in your credit card information and abandoned our payment page. 

When your membership or subscription purchased by you from a Partner Site, using our payment services, is about to expired, we may offer you to renew your membership or subscription. We may do this by contacting you through your email address or telephone number. 

You receive these communications because you have consented or/and because you have purchased a service or product using our payment services. You have the option to opt-out for free of our marketing communications at any time by contacting us at: [support@vendoservices.com](mailto:support@vendoservices.com)

  * **Off-site marketing and communications**

When signing up or purchasing a Product or Service from a Partner Site, you might be offered, on the payment page, to purchase a related or complementary trial or special subscription from another Partner Site. This Product or Service is not based on any profiling or user’s data behaviour analytics, but on an aggregated service. If you purchase such a related or complementary Product or Service your personal data, such as (but not limited) name, surname, username, password, user ID, email address and IP address may be passed on to such third party Partner Site, for providing you with complementary right access. We will not be held liable for the content of the Partner Site’s communications or products/services they are promoting. If you have purchased such a related or complementary service, you can opt-out at any time for free. To do this, please be advised that you will be required to contact the individual Partner SIte who have been marketing to you if you wish to stop receiving their communications directly. Note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites, nor we control or warrant the utility, merchantability or workmanship of the products or services offered at third-party websites

###  5\. How  protect your Personal Data 

It is ’ goal to provide its customers with a safe and secure shopping experience.

Vendo implements security measures according to applicable law to prevent unauthorised access or use, destruction or modification of your personal data.

is PCI compliant, and conforms with the security measures of the Payment Card industry.

’ secure server encrypts all your personal information (including name and address) so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the internet. When you enter this information it is captured on a page that uses the Secure Socked Layer (SSL) protocol by default. In order to be certain that you are connected to a real  payment window, you can click on the little lock that appears at the bottom of the window as soon as the connection has been made secure. Then check whether you are connected to a  server.  makes use of a 128 bits Thawte certificate for the payments pages and we use 3Des encryption for the credit card authorisation.

###  6\. How  use Cookies? 

Finally, like most websites, we process small pieces of information, called cookies on your computer's hard drive. This information is required to provide you with our services at the same time it enable us to improve and optimize your user experience.

Please read our Cookies Policy [here](https://secure.vend-o.com/page/cookies/).

**Use of Analytics programs** :

To optimize our services we use analytics programs. This website uses:

**Company Name**

| 

**Country**

| 

**Data Processing**  
  
---|---|---  
  
Google Inc

| 

USA

| 

IP address

Web activity report

No personal data shared  
  
###  7\. Your right to Information, Amendment or Deletion 

You have the right to view, access, rectify, erase, restrict, cancel and object to the processing of your personal data and settings of your user account at any time. We would like to point out that your right to the rectification or deletion of data may be restricted by law, including statutory retention periods and money laundering obligations, which we must observe. Furthermore, courts, judicial authorities or certain additional legal authorities may access data or demand information on a legal basis.

You may also revoke your consent of use of your voluntarily provided information at any time, by emailing us at **[support@vendoservices.com](mailto:support@vendoservices.com)**. Please acknowledge that the revocation of certain data could prevent us from carrying out our services within the framework of our offer.

For requests pertaining to access,rectify, erase, restrict, cancel and object data, please send a mail, along with your name, mobile number, date and amount of the charges, email contact address and your user name, to the following address: **[support@vendoservices.com](mailto:support@vendoservices.com)**. We may take additional steps to verify your identity before proceeding to comply with the request.

Where requests from a user are manifestly unfounded or excessive, in particular because of their repetitive character,  may either:

  a. charge a reasonable fee taking into account the administrative costs of providing the information or communication or taking the action requested; or  
  b. refuse to act on the request. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website you can contact: [support@vendoservices.com](mailto:support@vendoservices.com).

###  8\. International Personal data transfer 

For the provision of  services your personal data may be transferred to international entities located in the  following and non-exhaustive list of the countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA).

Argentina – Canada – Honduras – Israel – New Zealand – Switzerland - United States - Uruguay

These countries may not provide an adequate level of protection in relation to the processing of personal data (as decided by the European Commision), however we have entered into contractual safeguards with our service providers, according to the Article 28 of the EU General Data Protection Regulation. For more information please contact our EU representative  S.L at the email address above.
